- [laughs] I can't believe
you think Snuggle Squirrels One
is better than Snuggle Squirrels Two.
- I just think the snuggling is more believable
in the original.
- What about the third one?
The Empire Snuggles Back.
- I'm not discussing this with any of you
until you read the books.
- No, no, no.
The worst zombie movie ever is Zombabes.
最烂的僵尸电影是《僵尸宝贝》。
- I know. So lame.
我知道，太逊了。
Zombies aren't supposed to go to beach parties...or surf.
僵尸不应该去海滩派对...或者冲浪。
[both groaning]
[两人都发出呻吟声]
Give me the classic...
给我经典的...
"Must eat brains!"
“必须吃脑子！”
- Rwar! - Raaaahhh!
- 嗷！ - 啊啊啊！
- Oh. Maybe we shouldn't be
哦，也许我们不应该在
talking about this stuff in front of
孩子们面前谈论这些。
- [whispers] Kids. - [whispers] Yeah.
[低声] 对。
- Who, us?
- 我们吗？
Whaaaaat?
嗯～～？
We watch scary movies all the time.
我们经常看恐怖电影。
What else would we watch...
不看这个还能看什么...
Snuggle Squirrels? - Pfft!
柔软松鼠？ - 哼！
- Yeah. - I'm a snuggle squirrel!
- 是啊。- 我就是喜欢柔软松鼠！
- Who are you to judge us?
- 你凭什么评判我们？
- Then you must be really excited for tonight.
- 那你们今晚肯定很兴奋吧。
- Sure. Mom's meatloaf.
- 当然。妈妈的肉饼。
She adds paprika. It's a winner.
她加了辣椒粉，超好吃的。
- She's talking about Field of Brains...
她正在谈论《脑田》...
the scariest classic zombie movie ever.
史上最恐怖的经典僵尸电影。
It's on TV tonight.
今晚电视上会播放。
Uncut. Unrated.
未删减。无分级。
- And unbelievably scary!
而且可怕得难以置信！
[laughs] - Mm.
[笑] - 嗯。
- See you tonight. - Uh...
今晚见。 - 呃...
Obviously, we're watching Field of Brains tonight.
很明显，我们今晚要看《脑田》。
Duh!
废话！
- Guys.
伙计们。
You don't have to pretend.
你不必假装。
We all know you're too young for scary movies.
我们都知道你太年轻，不适合看恐怖电影。
And by the way...
顺便说一句...
the snuggle squirrels are adorable.
那些依偎的小松鼠真是可爱。
Like you guys.
就像你们一样。
- Did you hear that?
- 你听到了吗？
- Yeah.
- 是的。
She called me adorable.
她叫我可爱。
Our, "will they, won't they?" tension is electric.
我们的‘他们会，还是不会？’紧张感真是电光火石。
- She called us too young.
- 她说我们太年轻了。
That is the worst type of young.
那是年轻最糟糕的一种类型。
- She's right, though.
- 不过，她说得对。
We've never really seen a scary movie.
我们其实从未真正看过恐怖电影。
- Well, that ends tonight.
- 好吧，今晚就结束这一切。
We are watching Field of Brains.
我们要看《脑域》。
- I will be up here for one week,
- 我将在上面待上一周，
living on nothing but grit...
只靠毅力……
determination...
决心……
and the sweat from my socks.
还有我袜子上的汗水生存。
- All while promoting the affordably-priced camping gear
- 同时在这里推广价格合理的露营装备
here at Tom's Get Sporty. [laughs]
在这里的汤姆体育用品店。[笑]
- I'm not here to move tents, Harper.
- 我不是来卖帐篷的，哈珀。
Grizz Coyote's no sellout.
灰熊·科约特可不是个出卖灵魂的人。
[applause]
[掌声]
- Grizz is so rugged.
- 灰熊真是坚韧不拔。
He can survive anything. - I know.
他什么都能挺过去。 - 我知道。
I kinda hope a mountain lion gets loose in the store,
我有点希望店里跑进一只美洲狮，
just to see what happens. - [laughs]
就为了看看会发生什么。 - [笑]
- Wow. You guys are in a good mood.
- 哇。你们心情不错啊。
- Sure are.
- 确实不错。
- So, now would be a good time to ask you something? - Anything you want.
- 那么，现在是个好时机问你点什么吗？ - 任何你想问的。
- Can we watch Field of Brains tonight?
- 我们今晚能看《脑力战场》吗？
Both: No way. - What?
都不行。 - 什么？
- You're not watching a zombie movie.
- 你不看僵尸电影。
- Why not? - Because we've seen it.
- 为什么不？ - 因为我们已经看过了。
In a world where zombies eat farmers
在一个僵尸吃农民
and harvest their brains.
并收割他们大脑的世界里。
- Four kids will not see that movie
- 四个孩子不会看那部电影
because they are too young.
因为他们还太小。
- You guys are so mean.
- 你们太刻薄了。
- We're not mean. We're good parents.
- 我们不刻薄。我们是好父母。
There are certain disturbing images
有些令人不安的画面
we don't want you exposed to.
我们不想让你们接触到。
- [spits]
- [吐口水]
- Kids, look. Grizz is treating an open wound
- 孩子们，看。格里斯正在用他的脚趾甲和痰液处理一个开放性伤口。
with just his toenails and phlegm.
- 在这样的世界...
- In a world...
父母过于保护...
where parents are overprotective...
四个孩子无论如何都会看《脑田》。
four kids watch Field of Brains anyway.
- 我希望我们是那些孩子。
- I wish we were those kids.
- [欢快的音乐]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[有节奏的拍手] - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na-na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- Excuse me, Mr. Coyote.
对不起，郊狼先生。
We have a hypothetical question for you.
我们有一个假设性的问题要问你。
- Is it: Can a man walk barefoot across Alaska?
是不是：一个人能赤脚走过阿拉斯加吗？
Because yes. I did that.
因为是的，我做到了。
- Our question is about putting two bears to bed so we could--
我们的问题是关于哄两只熊睡觉，这样我们就可以——
I don't know-- watch a movie or something.
不知道——看场电影或者别的什么。
- We talking polar? Kodiak?
我们在说哪种熊？北极熊？科迪亚克熊？
Panda? - Mama.
熊猫？ - 妈妈熊。
About yay tall with blonde hair.
大约这么高，金发。
- And a 6' papa bear with a sort of
还有一个6英尺高的爸爸熊，有点像秃顶的吉姆·凯瑞。
balding Jim Carrey look.
异国情调的品种。
- Exotic species.
你们有任何矛或手榴弹吗？
Do you have access to any spears or grenades?
不，我们只是想帮助他们入睡。
- No, we just want to help them fall asleep.
好吧，既然你们没有手榴弹...
- All right, since you don't have any grenades...
我建议营造一个放松的氛围和一顿丰盛的晚餐。
I would recommend a relaxing atmosphere and a filling meal.
火鸡肉。
Turkey.
浓稠的肉汁。
Thick, heavy gravy.
通心粉和奶酪。
Mac and cheese.
也许再来个派。
Maybe a pie.
或许来个派。
- You've fed that stuff to bears?
你给熊喂过这些食物吗？
- No. But it puts my Uncle Jerry to sleep every Thanksgiving.
没有。但每年感恩节这些食物都能让我叔叔杰瑞睡着。
And he's pretty hairy, so...
他毛发挺茂盛的，所以...
- Hey, guys. What's up?
嘿，伙计们。怎么了？
- You guys getting grizzy with it?
你们在搞什么鬼？
- Yeah, we're gonna go home and floss with our shoes.
是啊，我们打算回家用鞋子剔牙。
- See ya.
再见。
- Hey, Grizz.
嘿，格里斯。
Camping sales are way up.
露营用品销量大增。
People love tough guys like you and me.
人们喜欢像你我这样的硬汉。
- You and me?
- 你和我？
Have you ever throat-punched a giraffe
你有没有因为长颈鹿咬了你的树枝而给它一记喉拳？
'cause he was eating off your branch?
你有没有让蟒蛇吞了你，就为了有个暖和的地方睡觉？
Have you ever let an anaconda swallow you
- （清喉咙）
so you'd have a warm place to sleep?
看到那道疤了吗？
- [clears throat]
那是我去年在森林里留下的。
See that scar?
- 在阿斯彭的一个豪华小屋里。
I got that last year living in the woods.
他发现没有无线网时，打了迷你冰箱一拳。
- In a luxury cabin in Aspen.
- [笑声] 好吧，我记得有人不肯吃烤棉花糖。
He punched a mini-fridge when he realized there was no Wi-Fi.
他一发现没有Wi-Fi就捶了迷你冰箱。
- [laughs] Okay, as I recall, someone wouldn't eat s'mores
好吧，我记得，有人因为棉花糖碰到了棍子就不肯吃烤棉花糖。
because the marshmallows touched stick.
因为棉花糖碰到了棍子。
- Those sticks were on the ground.
那些棍子在地上。
- They fell from a tree. That's where sticks land.
它们是从树上掉下来的。棍子就是那样落地的。
- Please!
拜托！
Civilians like you could never live off the land.
像你这样的平民根本无法在野外生存。
You sell the survival lifestyle.
你卖的是生存生活方式。
I live it.
我活在其中。
You want to know what tough is?
你想知道什么是艰难吗？
You should read my man-oirs.
你应该读读我的自传。
Which I wrote entirely on the hide of a rhinoceros.
那可是我用犀牛皮纸亲手写成的。
You know how hard it is to get a rhino to hold still that long?
你知道要让一头犀牛保持那么长时间的静止有多难吗？
Now if you'll excuse me...
现在，如果你们不介意的话...
it's lunchtime.
该吃午饭了。
- Is he right?
- 他说得对吗？
Have we gone soft?
我们是不是变得软弱了？
- No, no, no. We're still tough.
- 不，不，不。我们依然坚强。
We don't need that book.
我们不需要那本书。
- Mr. And Mrs. Harper!
- 哈珀先生和哈珀太太！
Your walk-no-mores have arrived.
- Yes! Finally, getting the mail
won't be so exhausting. [laughs]
- Okay, maybe we need to read the book. - Yeah.
Do you smell turkey?
- Yeah. - Huh.
- Oh. Oh. You know, according to Grizz...
that means either an avalanche is coming...
- Okay. - Or someone's cooking turkey.
- But it's meatloaf night.
- Kids!
孩子们！
Avalanche!
雪崩！
Oh. False alarm.
哦，虚惊一场。
It was turkey.
是火鸡。
- Welcome, parents.
欢迎，家长们。
Please sit.
请坐。
- What's going on in here?
这里发生了什么？
- We made you dinner.
我们为你们准备了晚餐。
- But what about my meatloaf?
那我的肉末糕呢？
- We're shaking things up.
我们改变了一下。
Tonight, we're having turkey
今晚，我们吃火鸡
covered in a thick, heavy gravy.
上面浇着浓稠的肉汁。
- Followed by more turkey, also with thick, heavy gravy.
- 接着还是火鸡，同样配以浓稠的肉汁。
- And for your dining entertainment,
- 为了您的用餐娱乐，
I'll be reading from a thick, heavy book.
我将朗读一本厚重的书。
Doorknobs: A Complete History.
《门把手：一部完整的历史》
- Are you guys trying to put us to sleep?
- 你们是不是想让我们睡着？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Chapter one.
- 第一章。
- More thick, heavy gravy?
- 又是浓稠的肉汁？
- Would you kids mind if we-- [yawns]
- 孩子们，你们介意我们-- [打哈欠]
If we, uh... - If you went to bed?
如果我们，呃... - 如果你们去睡觉？
Not at all.
一点也不。
Good night.
晚安。
- Love you. - Sweet dreams.
- 爱你。 - 做个好梦。
- Have a great sleep. - Don't let the bed bugs bite.
- 睡个好觉。 - 别让床虫咬了。
- Love you guys. - Good night.
- 爱你们。 - 晚安。
- Good night. - Good night.
- 晚安。 - 晚安。
- It's zombie time.
- 僵尸时间到了。
All: Rwar!
所有人: 嗷！
- And now... Field of Brains.
现在...《脑域》
- I've been dreaming about seeing this movie
我一直梦想着能看到这部电影
for as long as I can remember.
从我能记事起。
- You mean since this morning?
你是说从今天早上开始？
- Yeah. Like I said.
是的。就像我说的。
- Shh. The movie's starting.
嘘。电影开始了。
- "Based on actual events"?
“基于真实事件”？
Interesting.
有意思。
Man: Family? I've returned from farming.
男人：家人？我从农场上回来了。
Boy: Welcome home, Papa. Did you harvest any corn today?
男孩：欢迎回家，爸爸。你今天收割玉米了吗？
- Sure did, son. Sure did.
- 当然有，儿子。当然有。
- This isn't scary.
- 这并不吓人。
- Yeah, it's just a nice family
- 是啊，这只是个温馨的家庭
living on a farm in the middle of nowhere
- 住在荒无人烟的农场里
with no neighbors or police for miles.
- 方圆几英里都没有邻居或警察。
- I don't see how this could go wrong.
- 我看不出这会有什么问题。
Man: I'm gonna check the basement
男人: 我要去地下室
to see if the furnace is still acting up.
看看炉子是不是还在出问题。
[hinges creaking]
[铰链吱吱作响]
- Ooh. Ooh!
- 哦。哦！
Look at that doorknob.
看看那个门把手。
That's a rare 1937 lock and slide with Amish movement.
那是罕见的1937年锁和滑动装置，带有阿米什运动。
All: Shh!
嘘！
- Whoo-hoo! Sure is dark down here.
哇呼！这里确实很黑。
- [growling] - Aah!
（咆哮声）啊！
- It went so wrong so quickly!
事情错得这么快！
- [stomach gurgles]
（肚子咕噜声）
- Oh...
哦...
Tom, are you okay?
汤姆，你还好吗？
- Ah. I think the kids'...
啊。我想是孩子们的...
thick, heavy gravy...
浓稠厚重的肉汁...
might've hurt my stomach.
可能伤到我的胃了。
Grizz is right. We have gone soft.
格里斯说得对。我们变得软弱了。
- What do you mean "we"?
- 你说“我们”是什么意思？
My stomach is just fine.
我的胃一点问题都没有。
[stomach gurgles]
[肚子咕噜声]
Whoa.
哇。
Okay, that is not a sign of softness.
好吧，那不是软弱的迹象。
That is the call of the wild.
那是野性的呼唤。
- It sounds like a call for help.
- 听起来更像是在求救。
And a true survivalist doesn't call for help.
真正的生存者不会呼救。
We play through... [stomach gurgles]
我们要坚持下去...[肚子咕噜声]
- Okay, wait, wait, wait. Are you suggesting
等等，等等，等等。你是说
that you are more of a true survivalist than me?
你比我更像一个真正的生存者吗？
- Well, I don't want to toot my own horn, but...
嗯，我不想自吹自擂，但是...
Honk honk.
嘟嘟。
- Please! I am definitely
拜托！我绝对
more of a survivalist than you.
比你更像个生存者。
Honk honk.
嘟嘟。
- I could live outside for a week--honk.
我可以在户外生活一周——嘟。
- I could live outside for a month--honk.
- 我可以在户外生活一个月——哞。
- I could live outside right now.
- 我现在就能在户外生活。
No honk necessary.
不需要哞。
Oh, yeah. This is happening.
哦，是的。这就要开始了。
- Oh, what, pillows and a blanket?
- 哦，什么，枕头和毯子？
What, are you staying at the Queen's house?
什么，你要住在女王家里吗？
Give me the cold grass, baby.
给我冷草地，宝贝。
- Grass?
- 草地？
Oh, your majesty!
哦，陛下！
I'll take the hard dirt.
我选择坚硬的泥土。
- I hope it rains.
- 我希望下雨。
- I hope it snows!
- 我希望下雪！
- Honk! - Honk!
- 鸣！ - 鸣！
Honk. Ow!
鸣。哎哟！
Ah-ooga!
啊-噢嘎！
[screaming and snarling]
[尖叫和咆哮]
- Why are we still watching this?
- 我们为什么还在看这个？
- I'm too scared to turn it off.
- 我太害怕关掉它了。
- We have to keep watching.
- 我们必须继续看。
It's what the big kids do. [screaming continues]
这是大孩子们做的事。[尖叫继续]
Right, Nicky?
对吧，Nicky？
- The farmer has passed the first stage of zombification.
- 农夫已经通过了僵尸化的第一阶段。
Moaning and night walking.
“呻吟和夜间行走。”
The second stage is the digging of holes.
“第二阶段是挖掘洞穴。”
- Please don't dig holes. Please don't dig holes.
- 请不要挖洞。请不要挖洞。
[digging] [gasps]
[挖掘声] [喘气]
- Okay. He dug holes.
- 好吧。他挖了洞。
But at least he hasn't planted any brains yet.
但至少他还没种下任何脑子。
- Must plant brains.
- 必须种下脑子。
All: No!
所有人：不！
- Ugh, this ground is hard.
- 哎，这地真硬。
- You know, while you complain,
- 你知道吗，你抱怨的时候，
I'm building a bed out of nature.
- 我正在用大自然打造一张床。
- Oh, you think ripping off your sleeves like Grizz
- 哦，你以为像格里斯那样撕掉袖子
makes you a better survivalist?
就能成为一个更好的生存者？
That is pathetic. - Huh.
那真是可悲。 - 哼。
See, I must have left my sleeves...
看，我一定是把我的袖子……
over there.
留在了那边。
- Oh, you want a muscle show? - Yeah.
- 哦，你想看肌肉秀？ - 是的。
- Yeah, well get ready for the grand prize 'cause...
- 是啊，那就准备好迎接大奖吧，因为……
it's a new shirt.
这是一件新衬衫。
[saw buzzing]
[zombie growls] - Aah! Aah!
[crunch] Aah!
[snarling] [saw buzzing]
[soft music plays]
- The credits.
片尾字幕。
The sweet, sweet credits.
甜美的片尾字幕。
- We did it.
我们做到了。
We survived Field of Brains.
我们成功度过了《脑域》。
Pfft. Too young.
哼，太嫩了。
We are not too young.
我们不年轻。
- Yeah.
是啊。
We're not little kids who run to our Mom and Dad.
我们不是那种一遇到事就跑去找爸爸妈妈的小孩。
- [growling]
（低吼声）
- Wha--
什么--
Mom? - Dad?
妈妈？
- Dad!
爸爸？
- Mom! - Dad!
妈妈！
- Mom?
爸爸！
- Dad?
- 爸爸？
- Huh? Uh--
- 啊？呃--
- Mom? - Dad?
- 妈妈？ - 爸爸？
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
[growling]
- [咆哮]
- [growling]
- Mom? - Dad?
- 妈妈？ - 爸爸？
- Zombies.
- 僵尸。
- [moaning]
- [呻吟]
All: Aah!
所有人: 啊！
- Okay, everybody calm down.
好的，大家冷静下来。
Mom and Dad aren't zombies.
妈妈和爸爸不是僵尸。
Zombies aren't real.
僵尸不是真的。
- She's right.
她说得对。
Field of brains was just a movie.
《脑场》只是一部电影。
- Based on actual events.
是根据真实事件改编的。
Right, Nicky? Where's Nicky?
对吧，尼基？尼基在哪儿？
[stomach rumbles]
（肚子咕噜声）
- Gah.
啊。
Ah, I think the gravy train's leaving the station.
啊，我想是时候去吃点东西了。
Ooh. Oh.
哦。哦。
- Hey, hey, hey. Where are you going, nature boy?
嘿，嘿，嘿。你要去哪儿，自然男孩？
According to Grizz's book,
根据格瑞兹的书上说，
bathrooms are for daisy-sniffers.
厕所是给那些闻雏菊的人用的。
- I hate the smell of daisies.
我讨厌雏菊的气味。
- Well, then start digging.
那么，开始挖吧。
- Fine.
好吧。
[stomach gurgling] - Oh...oh...
哦...哦...
- Don't look at me.
别看我。
This hole is occupied.
这个坑已经有人了。
Ah!
啊！
- They've got Nicky. - Nobody has anybody.
他们抓了尼基。没有人有任何人。
Nicky is still upstairs.
尼基还在楼上。
- Yeah...
是啊...
and if Mom and dad were really zombie brain farmers,
如果爸爸妈妈真的是僵尸脑农，
wouldn't they be digging holes right now?
他们现在不应该在挖洞吗？
[both growling and groaning]
（两人咆哮和呻吟）
They're digging holes.
他们在挖洞。
- For our brains!
为了我们的脑子！
[groaning continues]
（呻吟继续）
- Listen to me if you want to live.
如果你想活命，就听我说。
While you were hiding under your pillows,
当你躲在枕头下时，
I saw it all.
我看到了一切。
I know what's coming.
我知道即将发生什么。
- Where'd you get the chalkboard?
你从哪儿弄来的黑板？
- Not important.
这不重要。
According to Field of Brains, Mom and Dad are not zombies yet.
根据‘大脑领域’，妈妈和爸爸还不是僵尸。
- Did you buy the chalkboard?
你是买的黑板吗？
- Forget the chalkboard.
忘了黑板吧。
Mom and Dad are just starting zombification process.
妈妈和爸爸刚刚开始僵尸化过程。
If this is about the chalkboard...
如果这是关于黑板的事...
It's just like in the movie.
这就像电影里演的那样。
- Stage one...
- 第一阶段...
moaning and night walking.
呻吟和夜间行走。
Stage two...
第二阶段...
digging holes.
挖洞。
- They're already on stage three.
- 他们已经进入第三阶段了。
- No, digging is stage two.
- 不，挖洞是第二阶段。
- Really? That's a shovel?
- 真的吗？那是个铲子？
- I thought he was trying to wood-fire a pizza.
- 我还以为他在尝试用木头烤披萨。
[distant growling, groaning]
[远处传来低沉的咆哮声]
- We don't have much time.
我们没有太多时间了。
The next stage is sensitivity to light.
下一阶段是对光的敏感。
Then... the final stage.
然后... 最终阶段。
They eat brains!
他们会吃大脑！
- What do we do?
我们该怎么办？
- Well, according to Professor Feldstein...
嗯，根据费尔德斯坦教授的说法...
- There is an antidote.
有一种解药。
But it must be administered before stage four.
但必须在第四阶段之前使用。
If not, they will become...
否则，他们会变成...
full...
完全...
blown...
爆发...
zombies. [voice echoes]
僵尸。
- Any questions?
有问题吗？
I found the chalkboard in the attic.
我在阁楼找到了黑板。
- Thank you!
谢谢！
- And a dirty sock.
还有一只脏袜子。
- Ugh, that antidote smells disgusting.
那个解药闻起来真恶心。
- Did you really think that dirty socks, toilet water,
你真的以为脏袜子、马桶水、
bellybutton lint, dead flies, moldy cottage cheese,
肚脐绒、死苍蝇、发霉的农家干酪、
dental floss gunk, and a sprig of dill
牙线残留物和一小枝莳萝
was gonna smell good?
会闻起来好闻吗？
- I thought the dill would jazz it up.
- 我以为莳萝会提提味。
- How are we supposed to get Mom and Dad to drink...
- 我们怎么能让爸爸妈妈喝...
this?
这个？
- We don't.
- 我们不用让他们喝。
We pour the antidote into their shoes.
- 我们把解药倒进他们的鞋子里。
It has to enter through their soles...
- 必须通过他们的脚底...
to save their souls.
- 来拯救他们的灵魂。
- That's deep, bro-fessor.
- 真有深度，兄弟教授。
- So, which one of you brave men
- 那么，你们这些勇敢的人中
wants to go downstairs and put it in their shoes?
谁愿意下楼去把解药放进他们的鞋子里？
So, which one of you brave men
那么，你们这些勇敢的人中
wants to take their fingernails out of my back?
谁愿意把我背上的指甲拔出来？
Boys: Sorry.
男孩们：对不起。
- Come on. We gotta find their shoes.
- 来吧。我们得找到他们的鞋子。
- I don't see them.
- 我没看到它们。
- Uh, let's check the back door.
- 呃，我们去后门看看。
- What if they come in?
- 如果他们进来怎么办？
- They won't, as long as the lights are on.
- 他们不会的，只要灯还亮着。
[both groaning]
[两人呻吟]
[electricity crackles] - Oh.
[电流噼啪声] - 哦。
Uh-oh.
哎呀。
That sounded like something important.
那听起来像是重要的事情。
Both: Oh!
两人: 哦！
- Definitely something important.
- 绝对是重要的事情。
- Aah! - Aah!
- 啊！ - 啊！
- Well, at least it's just us. - Huh.
- 好吧，至少只有我们。 - 嗯。
We should probably go inside and call the power company.
我们可能应该进去并打电话给电力公司。
Anonymously.
匿名。
- That's exactly what Grizz would do.
那正是Grizz会做的事。
- Yeah.
是啊。
- Ah! - Oh!
啊！- 哦！
Stepped in a hole!
踩到洞里了！
- Sprained my ankle.
扭伤了我的脚踝。
- [lisping] Bit my 'ongue!
[口齿不清]咬到舌头了！
- Ohh...uhh.... - Ohhhhhhh!
哦...呃....- 哦！
- Sprains. - S'rains!
扭伤了。- 扭伤了！
[both groaning]
[两人呻吟]
- Sprains... - S'rains...
扭伤了...- 扭伤了...
- Ooh.
哎哟。
- What are they doing?
他们在干什么？
- I think they're sitting down to eat.
我想他们正坐下来吃饭。
- Oh, no. They've reached stage four.
哦，不。他们已经到了第四阶段。
They're hungry for brains.
他们渴望吃脑子。
- [lisping] My tongue is on fire!
- [口齿不清] 我的舌头着火了！
- Stains!
污渍！
- Oh, stains! - Ugh!
哦，污渍！- 呃！
- Quick--we have to get the antidote in their shoes.
快——我们必须把解药放进他们的鞋子里。
- Aah!
啊！
- Huh?
嗯？
Huh? - Uhh?
All: Aah!
啊！
- Hey! Ehhhh....
嘿！额....
- Nooooo!
不！！！
- They got Ricky! Should we save him?
他们抓走了瑞奇！我们要救他吗？
Sorry, Ricky!
对不起，瑞奇！
- Go, go, go.
快，快，快。
[panting] We lost Ricky.
喘气声 我们失去了瑞奇。
- He's one of them now.
他现在是他们的一员了。
- I call his computer.
我给他的电脑打电话。
- We need to find Grizz.
我们需要找到Grizz。
He'll know what to do. He can survive anything.
他会知道该怎么做。他什么都能挺过去。
- Gah!
啊！
- Aah! - Aah!
- He's not here.
他不在这里。
[sloppy eating noise]
（狼吞虎咽的声音）
- What's that?
那是什么？
Grizz?
Grizz？
[rustling, lips smacking]
（窸窣声，咂嘴声）
- Aah! - Aah!
啊！
[all screaming]
所有人尖叫
- Aah! - Aah!
啊！
- Grizz has turned, too!
Grizz也变异了！
- It's a zombie apocalypse.
僵尸末日来了。
- Aah! - Aah!
啊！
- What? - Nicky!
什么？Nicky！
- I'm a goner.
我死定了。
- Dawn! - Aah!
Dawn！啊！
Aah!
啊！
Don't eat my brains. Don't eat my brains.
别吃我的脑子。别吃我的脑子。
Why aren't you eating my brains?
你为什么不吃我的脑子？
- Because I'm not a zombie.
因为我不是僵尸。
- Me neither.
我也不是。
- Not blood.
不是血。
Barbecue sauce.
烧烤酱。
- What about Grizz?
那Grizz呢？
- Hey. Is that takeout pizza and ribs?
嘿。那是外卖披萨和排骨吗？
- Hold on. I can explain.
等等。我可以解释。
I was really hungry.
我真的很饿。
- So you're a fraud?
- 所以你是个骗子？
- What do you mean by fraud?
- 你说的骗子是什么意思？
- You're a liar.
- 你就是个撒谎者。
- Oh, then yes, I'm a fraud.
- 哦，那没错，我是个骗子。
- Wow. Can you believe this guy?
- 哇。你能相信这家伙吗？
You must be really upset with him right now.
你现在一定对他很生气。
We'll let you hash it out.
我们会让你自己解决的。
- Hey, hey, hey. Wait, wait, wait. Come back here. - Hey!
- 嘿，嘿，嘿。等等，等等，回来。 - 嘿！
- Look, we told you guys that you couldn't watch that movie because we knew it would get in your heads.
- 听着，我们告诉过你们不能看那部电影，因为我们知道它会影响你们。
- You're just not old enough to see stuff like that.
- 你们还太小，不能看那种东西。
All: Yeah.
大家：是啊。
- We're sorry we watched Field of Brains.
- 我们很抱歉看了《脑域》。
- We're happy you're not zombies.
- 我们很高兴你们没有变成僵尸。
- All right. Bring it in. Come on.
- 好吧，过来，来吧。
There we go. - Aw, hugs.
这样就对了。 - 哦，拥抱。
- Yeah, this feels right.
- 是的，这样感觉对了。
I'll call my Mom. Have her pick me up.
我会给我妈妈打电话，让她来接我。
- Okay, maybe we can all go home and get some sleep
- 好的，也许我们现在都可以回家睡一觉，
now that we know that there's no such thing as zombies.
既然我们知道没有僵尸这种东西。
- Brains!
- 脑子！
- Zombies are real! Everybody panic!
僵尸是真的！大家快慌起来！
[screaming]
（尖叫声）
- No, no, no. Wait!
不，不，不。等等！
No, no, no. Guys, guys.
不，不，不。伙计们，伙计们。
[laughing]
（笑声）
I'm sorry. We were just messing.
对不起。我们只是在开玩笑。
- What are you guys doing here?
你们在这里做什么？
- We came from a Field of Brains party,
我们是从一个叫“脑域”的派对来的，
and I realized I left my phone here.
我意识到我把手机落在这里了。
- You look just like Abigail,
你看起来就像电影里的艾比盖尔，
the butter-churning farm maid zombie.
那个搅拌黄油的农场女仆僵尸。
- You saw the movie?
- 你看过那部电影？
- No big whoop. Could have been scarier.
- 没什么大不了的。本可以更恐怖些。
- Yeah, it takes more than that to rattle us.
- 是啊，光那样可吓不倒我们。
- They bought it.
- 他们上当了。
They actually think we're not zombies.
他们真的以为我们不是僵尸。
- I can't wait till they fall asleep
- 我等不及他们睡着了
so we can eat their brains.
这样我们就可以吃他们的脑子了。
[both growling]
[两人低吼]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Hey, lock up for us?
嘿，帮我们锁上门？
- Sure. - Thanks.
- 当然。 - 谢谢。
[continue growling]
[继续低吼]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- [cheerful melody]
- [欢快的旋律]
- ♪